Hey, Penny. Dumb-ass.
(Leonard:)Leslie Winkle.
(Sheldon:)Of all the overrated physicists
in all the labs in all the world...
(Sheldon:)...why does it have to be Leslie Winkle?
(Penny:)Well, they have a lot in common.
I mean, they're both scientists.
(Sheldon:)Please. The only way she could make
a contribution to science...
...would be if they resumed sending chimps
into space.
(Penny:)Okay, well, I have a date too,
so I'll see you.
(Sheldon:)Everybody has a date.
(Sheldon:)Even you, Mario,
going after Princess Peach.
And what am I doing?
I'm just enabling you.
- This is pretty good orange chicken.
- Yeah, it's from Chang's.
- Not Chow's?
- No, Chang's.
- What happened to Chow's?
- It changed.
(Leslie:)So how many children
do you think we should have?
[COUGHING]
(Leslie:)I'm sorry, that was a little abrupt.